Hey, I don't mean to interrupt
your little game...
(Penny(entering):)...but I thought you'd like to see what
you're missing out on. So, ahem, Bernadette?
(Penny(entering):)Bernadette's wearing leopard-print pumps
and a racktastic red dress from Forever 21.
(Penny(entering):)And there's Amy showing
all kinds of ankle...
(Penny(entering):)...in an outfit I'm assuming
is from Forever 63.
(Penny(entering):)And I myself...
(Penny(entering):)...am wearing a little number that got me
out of two speeding tickets and jury duty.
(Sheldon:)I know they're making a rhetorical point,
I just don't know what it is.
(Penny:)See you, boys. We are going drinking.
(Raj:)Wait. Can I come with you?
My character died.